Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Translation: RiKi66
--== ==-- Italianshare
www.italianshare.net
Section: ISubs Movies
Help!
Eddie!
What?
Eddie, wake up!
Do not move!
Whatever happens, do not move forward.
What's happening?
Hello.
want to make a game with you.
Devices on your head
are symbolic,
things like that
have done to others.
making risky loans
people without money
eliminating their financial
and their options
and asking
more than they could afford.
You are the predators.
But today, you will become prey.
and we should
a piece of your flesh,
- in the quantity you want.
- It's your fault
This is the way to
obtain freedom.
However, only one
you can survive.
Using the tools
the final sacrifice.
the sacrifice of flesh.
behind you
find the tools.
Be quick, you only have 60 seconds
Indeed when the timer will reach 0.
One who has sacrificed
more meat, is free.
Who lose  instead, will be placed
bolts in the brain.
Who  sacrifice more meat
to save?
make your choice.
I will not die because of you, bitch!
Saw VI
Translated by RiKi66
I asked Special Agent Strahm ...
has learned to trust me?
Because if you did not
this will always be your tomb.
of tea you will not know anything.
your body will never be found again,
and my inheritance will be yours.
make your choice
Hello, darling.
Well, listen, I am very,
very sorry
but I can not do it.
I have to work late.
I have a meeting with
my lawyer
and this will keep me busy
for the rest of the afternoon.
I know it's your birthday, but arrive
as soon as possible. I promise.
I love you.
- What were we talking about?
- We were talking of his deposition.
Do not worry about me, Debby. Small
lawyer who tries to pull a fast
fail to make me say
something I want.
I have no doubt, but
as a lawyer for this company
if you fucked up,
I am going to having to defend so ....
How about if we prepare a deposition?
- O Jesus!
- Remember the deal with Mr. Abbet Hill?
William, I have some Cassie Padern
on line 1.
Get the message Addy.
'll Call him this week ....
... maybe.
Continue.
When the Council will ask news about
Abbet the Lord, how shall I answer?
I will answer that as vice-president
this company
it is my duty
control any contract terminated.
Is it true that Abbet Sr.
was sitting right where she is sitting hours
when we discussed his contract?
I do not understand.
I have been with this company
insurance for over 10 years.
I know Harold, but unfortunately
When we reviewed your application
we discovered that she did not mention
its previous condition.
What condition?
There are no conditions.
It says here that you had an intervention
oral surgery at the level of the mandible.
's Absurd.
I have heart problems
that have nothing to do
- With an oral presentation made 13 years ago.
- Any oral intervention
leaves a scar.
The scars can lead
infections of the gums,
which as you know, can in turn
damage the heart.
.
You know what.
She is a murderess.
You're a fucking murderess.
I paid insurance for 10 years
without even a cold
and now I'm really sick
I want to reject the insurance cover?
- I have a family!
- These are the rules, Harold.
I'm sorry, but were your
actions to cause all this.
He just sentenced to death.
Now who will cover my medical expenses?
I was convicted.
I also have a family, because I can understand.
But practically the boy lied
its application.
- Be careful, Will.
- Why?
You think he did it on purpose?
It was not my place to judge
his actions
I was checking task
the accuracy of his claim.
Everyone thinks we're bad people.
No mention the various people who
help each year
without incident
or the millions of dollars
we give each year in benificenza
or all of the clinics
help you free ...
Short answer, Will.
Short answers.
The properties of one of the most
known killers,
John Kramer
have been redistributed.
Were mainly in real estate,
but to be precise ...
One last question.
Who found the error in its application?
We work with a team.
If there is an error in the applications
we find.
- Lord, are waiting in the conference room.
- Ok.
How are you today guys?
I found two errors in the application for a client.
This practice had now been closed for some time.
- Terminator strikes again!
- Be back in a few hours.
Farewell, Hank.
Who  sacrifice more meat
to save?
die because of you, bitch!
Yes?
Be right.
- What happened?
- You must go to the scene of the crime,
they want them
as soon as possible.
Erickson!
I did not think you'd ever
moved from behind your desk.
I made an exception for fingerprints
we found at the crime scene Jigsaw.
See GUI.
We have already passed in various databases.
- Did you identify with?
- Yes
By Peter Strahm.
When you find 'that he and Perez
were targets of Jigsaw,
I should be more careful,
but I would never have expected.
- Not by Peter Strahm.
- None of us would have thought it.
Yes, but ...
we have something of which he is not aware.
Seguimi
Lizzie.
Detetive Hoffman.
Perez?
It was my decision, detective.
I knew that Jigsaw was not working alone,
but until I knew for sure
who help themselves
I could not guarantee his safety.
So she made me believe that
dead?
Well, I did not know
who I can trust.
What else have I been hiding?
We know that the agent Strahm kidnapped
5 people in a real estate agency.
Victims who found Erickson.
- How did you know?
- Strahm and I investigated after the fire.
He said he had
be convicted
But after the witnesses will play
disappear
and the charges were withdrawn.
Strahm could make them flee,
then they would have caught, put into a trap,
massacrasi and have them bound to each other.
What then?
Revenge?
You call it as he wishes,
but must be captured.
We would like to work with
us on this case.
You made me believe that she was dead
and now you want to work with me?
Listen, we are offering the opportunity detective.
From now on, all that what
we know we will too.
Then accept?
Hoffman says that Detetive
a brief statement?
Pamela Jenkins.
- Just tell the truth detective.
- That's what's doing? John Kramer ...
If you would make a statement
I would be very happy to hear it.
Change facts
makes a better story?
Is his responsibility.
Excuse me, now I must go.
I know things about John Kramer
she even imagines.
- I doubt it.
- Kramer left a box at his wife.
- Did you know?
- Maybe yes, maybe no.
- How did you know?
- From the court.
This is a public archive,
very useful if you know where to look.
Okay, what you really want?
Jill Tucker.
Help me to get to her
and discover things sensational.
Really?
I see what I can do.
I do not know how I got there.
I just opened my eyes ... e.
I know who did this to me.
Who did this?
Jigsaw.
She has cut her arm on her own.
It's true I did,
but he forced me.
And why?
Because what we were doing
Eddie and I was wrong.
Ruined the lives of people.
He wanted me to learn the lesson.
And she did?
Look at me!
Look at my fucking arm.
What the fuck should I learn from this?
Look at my arm!
What?
What was I supposed to learn from this?
Look at me!
Hello Gillian!
I'm sure I put here, somewhere.
Look here.
This gives happiness to the family.
We love you more than ourselves son.
If you're looking at this  Jill
'm gone from this world.
I leave a box today
its content
is of great importance.
Now I'm not at home, but, please,
leave a message.
Sig.na Tucker, are still
Pamela Jenkins.
hoped it would clarify one thing
the relationship with her husband ...
Here  detective?
Listening to this will understand
that is wrong.
Now she thinks he has control,
is not it?
think to be able to get out before he risked his life?
Look here ...
These are the parts taken
of older victims of Jigsaw.
This is the piece taken
the last victim.
- They look the same.
- Yes, that's what we thought ....
The serrations indicate that the incision was made
with a serrated knife blade.
So?
Then all the other recordings were made
with surgical precision.
It is obvious that Strahm has used a different knife
from that used by John Kramer.
Yes, but this is strange, and so we
confrontanto various incisions.
Same knife
was used for another victim.
Seth Baxter.
The boy who killed his sister.
Are you saying that you know understand
knife which was used
just looking at the photos?
No, but I can not.
I was the one to examine his body.
I have reviewed all the victims of Jigsaw.
Excellent work.
Lacked the recorder in the last scene of the crime,
So, we are checking the tape Seth Baxter.
Why?
Well if someone other than the affected victims,
perhaps the same person has also recorded the tape.
- Strahm.
- Yes, maybe.
Strahm's voice on that tape
would be a smoking gun.
If so,
we could prove his involvement.
Jane. It's all ok.
Calm down.
I was not expecting to meet
so soon.
Change in plans.
The game must begin tonight.
Why?
Anyone know why the box,
and it should not.
- Who?
- Do not not know.
Everything you need to know is that
from now
I control all aspects of the game.
Is not what John would want to.
Give me the envelope.
Is not a request.
Here they are.
Is that all?
- Yes
- From now, I manage alone.
Okay.
I just want to meet
Last call for John.
Well, John is dead.
And his work is almost finished.
- What is this?
- A job to finish.
When I've finished
we speak.
Methadone is only a mask
is not a cure, but something that blurs the senses.
I found a better way.
These people ...
continue to hurt you,
till we fall.
Are drugged, John.
Cure requires a process.
The dependence is
part of human nature.
But what about these people,
Jill, who come here every day
and we use them?
They buy their time.
Avoid prison.
And you call this recovery?
- It's not so simple.
- The establishment is not so simple, Jill!
Wake up!
These people have no respect
for the lives they destroy.
But when they see death
fail to appreciate life.
And they understand the value of life.
This is my way.
And I guarantee that it works.
- Amanda?
- Hello, Jill.
Jill. You would not say that she
was a lost soul.
Instead it was.
Now it is cleaned.
And it is cured.
- Is able to appreciate his life.
- Works.
True.
Helped me.
Ok, John.
Although the police said that John Kramer,
called Jigsaw, had died,
prorpio last week claimed to have discovered
a new game with terrible implications.
the victims are all connected
the life of John Kramer ...
Jigsaw might be dead
But the killings continue.
Damn!
Hank, are you still here?
Do not move!
Shit!
O God!
Someone will take care of you.
Where is the key?
And in the left pocket?
Hello, William.
O God
Probably you never thought
that we would meet again.
- Today is that day.
- No!
For years, it was able to decide your
the fate of other people.
You have unjustly refused several times the possibility
to do good to people.
However, this now no longer matter.
Men want to live.
When they go to their death there is a clash
between those who want to live and who should live.
But today is different.
Today your past
be put to trial.
There are four straps wound around you
and four tests that must be overcome.
Because if you do not, the straps on your arms
and on your legs explode.
Looks good ..
You have 60 minutes to complete your test
or to leave your fate
from now.
You are not alone.
If he could not complete the tests before the timer
reaches 0, you'll never see more than your family.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, wake up!
Mom.
Where are we?
Do not know.
- What place is this?
- I do not know.
Watch ...
Oh, my God!
Here's your first test.
The health and your dirty past
brought you success.
This can not be said
your opponent.
Just turned 52 years, this man has continued to
smoking nonstante his heart problems.
This shows how
unappreciated his life.
Your goal will be to concentrate
on a simple element, the air.
When will this game
every time you breathe
The straps around your chest will approach
and crush your body.
The only way to save and hope for the death of another.
So I ask you, before death,
Who will survive?
Live or die, Will.
Make your choice.
- Fuck!
- What the fuck is going on?
Hold your breath.
What the hell?
Oh Jesus!
Dai!
Shit!
Please help us!
Help, please!
Please!
Help!
Please help!
Please!
Help!
Is anybody!
Live or die?
WTF?
Connected to that thing.
- What?
- Hydrofluoric acid.
This substance can corrode the flesh
in seconds.
- What do we do?
- I do not know.
Want to live, right?
But the timer?
Must mean something.
I have no idea. I do not know
why we are here.
We are here because of your father.
- Sig.na Jackness?
- Please, I need only a minute.
We can help each other.
Why think you can come to me
in this way?
Because I found something
that you will see.
There.
Where did you find us?
It was the place where he died Jhon.
It means something to you?
No.
Farewell, sig.na Jackness.
If she were up to something.
I want to thank you for having sponsored
this festival, Will.
And I know what has
appreciated by the clinic.
John Kramer.
Kramer, she is the husband of Jill
- Yes
- Pleased to meet you.
My pleasure.
We are in the same
bulb, John.
Why?
Although she tries to understand
Human behavior, then ....
When people come to us for medical coverage.
We have to analyze each person individually
to calculate its probability of success.
- How can you do?
- We have a formula.
It's actually quite complicated,
but,
practices take monthly payments
them multiplied by the charges made in a month
for the reduced risk of life
And if someone is positive
consider it recovered.
- Who created this formula?
- I.
So you practically chooses who lives
or who dies.
No, I decide just which people can
potentially live
live long and healthy.
But she is not taking into account
the most important element in this period.
And what?
I want to live.
When a presone is facing death
It is impossible to say what will
to survive.
Fuck!
Shit!
Hello, Will.
On the platform behind me, there are
two of your colleagues.
One is Clark.
A healthy man with no relatives or relations.
The atra, a woman of middle age.
With a family from the dark past.
According to the policy your secretary
is old and not ready to survive.
But you know that it would be a bad loss
for his family.
Instead seglie he would only be a small point
disappearing from radar.
Only one will leave this room alive
It's up to you to choose whom.
You can choose to save the life
one or the other.
As you can see, the choice is not so easy
when you're face to face
with people whose blood
The stain your hands.
The game begins.
Wait, no!
Not kill anyone!
Not kill anyone.
Help me.
This is a bulb.
The decisions are mine not theirs.
I will not.
Help me, please.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Find a way out of here, Addy
Careful.
Why not throw acid on the bars
iron corrode?
With what they threw it on the bars?
With hands?
What are you looking at?
Thought ...
Look at that mirror.
What?
Somebody's watching from behind the glass.
What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
Somebody help me, please.
Please help me.
Hello, Pamela.
You've done something sensational
in my life.
changing the truth
and using it to your advantage ..
Hoffman.
I  Erickson.
We found the tape Seth Baxter.
So?
But we have something else to discuss
with her face to face.
- What?
- Better to speak in person.
- It is very important.
- I'll be there soon.
The device you are trying,
is my favorite.
I called Articulator.
Last-minute adjustments?
If the speed is too high you
change speed gears
to coincide with the 'increase friction.
Maybe you should leave alone the difficulties
largest.
You will need this.
Come to me next time.
How many games will still be there?
How many will.
That is a human being
you like to treat him with brutality, Mark?
Let's be honest.
You want it to end
what I want it.
- So what was your test, detective.
- I do not need one.
- Really?
- Yes
Because I appreciate the value of life.
You are still
an ordinary mortal.
What do you know of life?
However're safe
I'm not going anywhere.
Are you sure?
Time is short.
You okay?
Go speak with Dr. Devon hospital.
Ok.
Be right back.
Go
Be quick.
- Why did you come?
- John.
Please, stop.
- Do not do it.
- Like I promised ...
When it's all over.
I will give you a way out.
I wish that time was now.
I have something for you.
What is it?
You will discover that in its time ...
know what to do.
final decision.
because I wanted to talk
I found a cure for my cancer
But my requests
Cover ...
have been rejected.
Therefore, I thought
that if I came here to explain it,
maybe you could help me.
We hear  John.
and a doctor, Norway,
the success rate is 30-40%
with his therapy.
He inept what are called
cell suicide, in
cancer cells.
So it is a form of toxicity
which is given by the active drugs (bho ????!!!).
I'm familiar with the therapy
which is speaking to me.
Okay.
Then when you start testing?
is looking for new patients.
- Am I supposed to be the perfect candidate.
- John.
If your doctor,
Dr. Gordon would have thought
it was a useful therapy
you would have thought.
Dr. Gordon is a specialist
making money and leading the people his experiments.
-not a thinker ...
I will be direct with you,
given his age and cancer
which is in an advanced state
not fall as the perfect candidate ...
Wait.
What's feasible?
What  mathematical equation
this is not feasible?
and politics, John.
Politics.
If you try to circumvent the system
to do this treatment is also ineffective
go against our policy
and we will take your medical coverage.
I'm sorry.
you know that people pay in the Far East
doctors, when they are well
But when they are sick
not have to pay?
Basically  pay for what they want,
not for what they do not want.
Here we started with the wrong foot.
these politicians always say the same things,
again and again.
Decisions regarding health should
be taken by patients and their doctors
not by the government. Today decisions
not be taken by doctors
their patients or the government,
but by
insurance companies.
Pirani ...
John  ...
please, if you do
you alone
and the costs incurred will be too high
I do not talk about money.
I will have the money.
These  principles.
You know ... is my life.
we're talking about, remember?
What about Jill? Who will take
care of her when there is more?
not worry about Jill.
The type of cancer that struck you
is malignant and inoperable.
Now his tone has become more subtle.
Although the treatment
work cancer will return sooner or later.
is a battle
missed the start.
is now even more subtle.
To tell the truth
is calm.
though I will not live much longer, I will
judge permanently.
because death
will not have mercy on your soul.
You made a mistake.
Hello, William.
now you're finding
defects in your policy,
but what you have not seen are the
devastating effects on people
face of death.
The lawyer of your company.
has 90 seconds to cross this room
or device attached to his chest
it will operate and she will die.
'll be fine.
You're the key to
survival.
That the game starts.
Listen!
Che ... What the hell is going on!
You have to overcome this corridor
quickly as possible!
Go, go now!
Come on, you can do it!
You have to keep moving.
Will, this is madness.
Go ...
Come on, you can do it to get out of here!
Wait a minute,
I think I can help here.
We must work concomitantly!
We must work concomitantly to succeed!
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
Go!
Keep moving, do not stop!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
I can not! It's a fucking trap!
There is no way out.
It's a fucking trap.
I can not get out!
No!
No, there is a ladder at the end!
If you get there, be able to help.
Are you ready?
Go!
Come on!
You're almost there.
Go! Go! Go!
Search for a key, there should be a key.
Come on!
- What are you waiting for?
- It is inside you.
- What?
- Is within you!
Shit.
Ok.
Or wait ... Wait what are you doing?
I can take it!
God, no!
Hello, Pamela.
Will today will test the significance
of a sacrifice.
And you will see the consequences of,
things done wrong to others.
Fuck!
Is anybody there.
Someone is watching.
Why?
Why someone would want to do this?
Thanks for coming.
What have you found?
- An anomaly in the fingerprints of Strahm.
- What?
Look.
Fingerprints leave human
residue Olioso.
Based on how long they
been exposed to a particular item
are more or less contaminated.
And what 's the problem?
We found traces of azometan R12.
Will the Freon.
The question is:
The sample we found was already there
or was Strahm in Porto?
We controllamo inside the 'edifício
before it was abandoned.
You get something from the tape of Baxter?
Yes
We found something.
The tape was in bad shape when we found,
but we were able to authenticate.
The voice was distorted intentionally, but
does not coincide with those of John Kramer.
They're looking at right now.
- To do what?
- To try to eliminate the distortion,
and find the original entry.
Is the technical department now.
Time does that mean?
Your watch.
Yes, I had it before coming here
We did.
This is our Carrier.
The lab is ready.
Dai.
Come along it?
Certain.
Hey! Who's there?
- Sr. Easton, was you?
- Ms. Shelby?
Who's with you?
We are all here, sir, all 6.
What the hell is going on?
What to see?
Nothing at all, it's dark.
- What is that sound?
- I do not know, but we are bound to something.
- turns.
- Take us out of here!
Please
Get us out of here.
Help,
Sr. Easton, help us.
Sr. Easton, please.
Help us get out of here.
Mr. Easton, what's going on?
A game.
game?
What the hell are you talking about?
Hello, Will.
front of you there are 6 of your
cooperation.
Those who find errors in applications.
find errors on two-thirds
applications
which are then discarded
or terminated.
time you apply your analysis
on them
in order to find their mistakes.
You are on the carousel
but only two will go down.
choose the two that will survive
is his job.
But remember that the weapon
continue to fire until all
six rounds will not be finished.
If you do not take any decision,
All six will die.
save someone
will crush both buttons
in the cage,
simultaneously.
Comuqne, for slave somebody
must make a sacrifice on his part.
Two can live,
4 die.
His decision is  rapprestentata
the blood on his hands.
I do not want to die here.
Listen, I have
live.
Shit.
Oh god!.
Please! Mr. Easton.
Mr. Easton. Please, Mr. Easton
Crush that button.
Crushes!
Poer please!
Sr. Easton, crush that button.
Sr. E!
He said we had to be the most
strong as possible.
But how can I be strong,
if you let me die.
Help me.
I have two children.
And they can not live without me.
Please, can not grow
without me.
Thank you.
I do not even know Mr. Easton.
My relatives are sick, and I
help. They have only me.
Do not say shit, your parents hate you.
We have thrown out.
- What? Not true.
- Yes, indeed.
- Tell me the truth.
- No it is not true.
He's lying.
Please. Please!
Help me!
He's lying!
No, no, no!
Damn!
My parents are rich.
I'll give you everything you want, you just saved me.
But if you do not see them for years!
Fuck!
God please save me, Lord. E.
Sr. Easton, please.
The consequences of this game
will be terrible.
I'm on your side.
I can help.
You can trust me.
Do not think, is lying.
It will continue to do so.
It's me, Josh.
Help me!
Fuck!
Oh is that so?
It's over.
Son of a bitch.
Are you a big piece of shit.
A fag shit.
Son of a bitch.
Then they?
You decide to save a bitch and it's all over?
True, William?
You're a piece of shit.
It's a bullshit!
A great bullshit.
Not true, the son of a bitch?
Look at me.
When you're killing me
Look into my eyes.
Oh my god!
Now
You feel helpless.
How are you?
Well.
Here we are.
Anyone who has seen the tape
had access
a crew of advanced sound filtering.
Now
You feel helpless.
Fortunately, we have a few tricks on our side.
Bypassing the algorithm used
we hear the true voice.
Let us hear what we have.
Now
You feel helpless.
You okay?
You seem a little worried.
Only just worried
for the tape.
You know there are some things
I still can not understand.
I do not understand the motivations of Strahm.
Has been my partner for 5 years.
Eu sabia que era com todo mundo
muito menos sobre a cabeça,
but I have not seen any sign
of psychotic behavior.
You can never know what happens
in the mind of a person.
... weak.
Did you hear?
There.
Come on, I thought I had something to show.
No, I never thought
it was a vengeful person.
Understand?
That is, all the facts are there.
But something has nothing to do.
Look, we're getting closer.
You know there is no alternative.
Suppose Strahm
has killed Seth Baxter
and part of
complex of Jigsaw.
Well.
Well then there is a problem.
Having thoroughly studied the fingerprints of
Strahm, we found that
Uric acid residues
not match
an individual
with an active metabolism.
In other words?
In other words, it means that the fingerprints
left on the 'last victim,
were left when Strahm was already dead.
I've done.
Now
You feel helpless.
Who knows me?
All.
You're lying.
You're lying, bitch.
I found something that might interest you.
was the place where he died Jhon.
not mean anything to you?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to finish this
as soon as possible.
We do not know what will happen.
Do not just sit here doing nothing.
We must make a decision,
Do not you understand?
Ok.
You can pull it.
I love you.
I love you too.
Departed.
No. I do not know what will happen.
At the three draft.
No. No.
One ...
Two ...
Three!
WTF?
Not work.
This thing does not work.
WTF?
I think I know what it is used.
Leave him to me,
I will not go anywhere.
Are you sure?
Amanda  betray you.
We'll see.
Amanda, you'll see ...
What are you doing?
Vai.Vai!.
drie  what does not want?
Get out of here.
Go!
Listen .
You killed that child.
You know, and I know.
so you have to do exactly
what you say.
Kill Denlou Lynn,
'll tell Jhon  or what you did.
deserves to go.
Amanda is more important
what you think.
I 'done!
I've done it!
I've done it!!
If it fails,
no more shall never see your family again.
- What are you doing here?
- Will.
Pamela.
Yes
I know it's your birthday.
I will do as fast as possible, I promise.
you really want to leave alone
your sister to stay at work?
're my only family.
You okay?
Let her go.
'T get it. Won.
Shit, I followed your fucking rules.
Now let it go.
Son of a bitch.
He just sentenced to death
Now who will pay the costs.
I've just condemned.
You're the man who killed my father.
Hello, Tara.
I offer my deepest apologies to you and your son
for having reserved this treatment.
But I assure you that I
done for a reason
The man in front of you
you just sarificato to save
the lives of others.
However, had the opportunity
to save the life of her husband,
and chose not to.
Now you have the power
to save a life.
Will you give this man the opportunity
to continue to live,
or give him the same sentence of death
he has given to her husband?
live or die.
Vate your choice.
It is not my game.
I leave a box today.
content
is of extraordinary importance.
Miss.Tucker, what's in the box?
Please.
Please forgive me.
Have mercy, please.
She mercy
when my husband was suffering?
John has left 5 envelopes.
the sixth was for me.
This is the will of Jhon.
- He had no other choice.
- There is always a choice.
Let me tell you something.
It is not because I can not forgive
for what I did.
The reason for what I am doing
is that I can not forgive myself
to do anything to another person.
Please, no.
- You never want to feel that way.
- Please.
I can not.
I can.
No, Brent.
You killed my father, the son of a bitch.
Now burn in hell.
These are the rules, Harold.
He just ordered
death.
sense.
you choose who lives and who dies.
Politics, John. Politics.
Who created the formula?
Although I will not live much longer
I who will judge you for last
and the devil will take your soul.
're making a mistake.
Game over.
No.
What is your test,
Mr. detetive?
I do not need one.
Really?
know why you're here, right?
You must learn what it is used,
what it takes to survive.
think you have real control,
is not it?
think of being able to go
without having addressed your test.
I care only that the last
Jhon desire to be heard.
You like to treat him with brutality, Mark?
From now on,
I take control of the game.
not what you would like Jhon.
want a chance?
I'll give you a chance.
--== ==-- Italianshare
www.italianshare.net
Section: ISubs Movies
Translation: RiKi66
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org